[♪ theme music playing]
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
CHARACTERS, EVENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND PLACES IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
[high-pitched ringing]
[♪ surreal music playing]
[explosion]
[Haran] What is it?
Are you okay?
[♪ music fades]
Yes, it was just the lights.
I'm fine.
No, you don't look fine.
I am.
I won't cause you any trouble,
especially during the three-month trial.
[sighs]
[chuckles softly]
[Chan] It was my first time
hearing that sound.
[♪ pensive music playing]
It kind of sounded like tiny bits
of metal clinking or ice rattling.
Right, the door!
I think it came from outside the lab.
EPISODE 4
But I'm not sure what that sound was
or why I was suddenly reminded
of the explosion.
[doctor breathes deeply]
From everything I've heard so far,
it's most likely
that it's a second trigger.
A second trigger?
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Song Haran, the lead designer.
[doctor] It seems that
seeing her again acted as a trigger.
She seems to have stimulated something,
allowing you to remember
another piece of your past.
[chuckles] Wait. No…
[stutters] That doesn't make any sense.
I recalled everything seven years ago.
When I first saw her at Jamsugyo,
I remembered everything in Boston.
How are you sure it was everything?
Well, because it was only
a temporary side effect
from the shock of the accident.
You're saying you remembered
everything at that moment?
Yes. And I've never recalled
any new sounds or images since then.
Not once.
What if…
-Like this…
-[eraser scraping]
What if there is still an empty spot
in your memories that you're not aware of?
An empty spot?
[doctor] You seem like
a completely different person now.
I can even picture
how hard you tried to change yourself.
The harder you try to shake off the past,
the more your defense mechanisms kick in.
Your unconscious mind
may overwrite painful memories
to keep you from suffering any longer.
It means there's still
an empty spot inside you.
[Chan] If that sound
is a part of that empty spot,
is it a signal from the past
telling me it's linked
to the explosion seven years ago?
[doctor] We can't be sure
of anything right now, but…
it's certain that
she's the one who has the key
to that empty spot inside you.
-[water gushing]
-[♪ music fades]
You don't seem happy to see me.
I mustered up my courage
to come and celebrate starting the trial.
That's cold!
Mmm. I always give a water show
to people I'm excited to see.
-[scoffs]
-[Chan chuckles]
Hey, look who it is!
[exclaims] How have you been, Genius?
-[Genius barks]
-[Haran chuckles]
-[Haran] How are you?
-It's been such a long time.
What are you doing here so early?
I wanted to have your coffee.
I'm aching
from not having any for so long.
Really? Then I should make you some now.
Come on in.
-Let's go, Genius.
-[Manjae] Come inside.
[doctor] If you don't want to suffer again
because of your past,
it would be best
to keep a distance from her.
To protect yourself,
a lock is safer than a key at the moment.
[whispers] A lock…
-[♪ heartwarming music playing]
-[sighs]
-[coffee pouring]
-[door opens]
-Sit down, roomie.
-Okay.
Here's some coffee for my VVIP.
Thank you. [inhales sharply]
[Chan] Huh?
Right. It must have recovered
from the transplant shock.
[sighs contentedly]
Good thing I repotted it, right?
[chuckles]
-Yes.
-[Manjae] Right. [chuckles]
It's a good thing you took it out.
Even if I break down again,
I'll stay by her side.
Mmm.
[Chan] She's the one
who gave me the life I have now.
I would have died
if it hadn't been for her.
Why are you staring at me?
Mmm… Can't I look at you?
Here. Cheers. [grunts]
[Haran slurps, sighs contentedly]
Whatever's hiding in that empty spot,
I'm going to deal with it.
As long as she becomes happy,
I don't care what happens.
I'll be careful
so my existence doesn't reopen
her old wounds…
and I'll do everything I can for her
before I leave again.
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
[♪ music fades]
Did you check the data?
Yes.
The background team's research
was a little lacking.
When did you organize all this?
There was a lot of modernized material,
so I researched traditional hanok.
I guess a Korean
should have researched traditional hanok.
[both chuckle]
[in English] Okay,
I'll send this over to the EA team,
and we can go down to Gyeongju on Tuesday.
[in Korean] Oh. I'll join you a day late.
Ms. Kim said she'll send over
the dancheong design draft on Tuesday.
[Ben in English] Mmm. Okay.
[in Korean]
But how will you get there, then?
-I'll rent a car.
-Are you sure?
I'll be absolutely fine.
[chuckles nervously]
Hey, stop writing that.
Fine.
-Geez!
-[Chan] We'd like to pay.
BEN IS AN IDIOT
Ms. Song!
[♪ whimsical music playing]
What is he doing?
You're done with work, right?
Are you busy, by any chance?
[in English] Nice!
[in Korean] Then get in.
-What? Where are we going?
-There's a car coming.
I have a special lecture tomorrow,
so wrap up the contract with our buyer.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Get in. Come on.
-[Chan] Watch your head.
-[car honks]
Sorry!
[in English] Oh, yeah.
[in Korean] Did you just say, "Oh, yeah"?
Those two.
Keep an eye on them.
Bye, then.
So they weren't lying to me.
[♪ music fades]
We came all the way here for chicken?
This is a must in Korea.
Hangang River, picnic mat, and chicken.
I'm also a tourist from abroad, you know.
Wow!
The Hangang River is so nice.
[♪ lighthearted music playing]
[chuckles softly]
I have something to give you. Sit down.
There are 0.3, 0.4, 5, 6,
oil-based, water-based,
nib tip, and ballpoint pens.
Wait. Are you opening a stationery store?
Who has this many pens?
I have a habit of buying new pens
for people who lose their pens.
-[sighs softly]
-[Chan sighs]
There should at least be
one pen that you like.
But the trial hasn't started yet.
This is like a preview.
A preview of what?
I'll be away for about two weeks
starting Wednesday
for a field survey.
I said we'd get close,
but if I left without doing anything,
nothing would change.
And I didn't want that.
So…
[♪ music fades]
will you take this, too?
Oh…
SEOUL DESTINATIONS LIST
Why are you giving this to me?
Choose where to go first
so we can go together later.
[cell phone buzzes]
[exclaims] The chicken's here.
I'll go get it.
[grunts] Can you clean that up?
Oh. It's this way.
We have to eat chicken here, so hurry!
"That person"?
[exclaims excitedly]
The night view is beautiful.
-Right?
-[camera clicks]
How about going to Jamsugyo on Christmas?
It's the best spot
-to watch the fireworks.
-[woman gasps]
-[woman] I'd love that. [giggles]
-Jamsugyo?
[couple] Cheers.
[♪ "Jingle Bell" playing over speakers]
[taxi driver] Goodness.
We're really stuck.
I heard they're showing fireworks
at 7:00. [sighs]
We're not moving at all.
[sighs]
How long will it take?
I have an important meeting.
If it's urgent, it would be faster
to just walk across the bridge.
Mr. Yoon.
The traffic's bad
since it's Christmas Eve.
Really?
Then take your time.
All right.
[call disconnects]
[♪ J.S. Bach "Goldberg Variations,
BWV 988: Aria" playing over speakers]
[firework whistles, pops]
[people exclaiming]
[Haran] Hey, Kang Hyeokchan.
Why aren't you picking up?
[Hyeokchan] Sorry, I fell asleep.
Maybe I have insomnia.
My sleep pattern is messed up,
so I'm sleeping at random times.
[Haran] They said it helps with insomnia.
Try listening to it
when you can't sleep. Okay?
[♪ music fades]
Let's go.
-What? Right now?
-Yes.
[man 1] Should we order fried chicken?
-Isn't seasoned chicken better?
-Hang on.
[man 2] No, fried is better.
-Here you go!
-[man 1] What's this?
You won some free chicken.
-We can have this? Wow.
-Of course.
[Chan] It's still warm, so enjoy.
[men] Thank you.
[Chan grunts]
Come on. These are valuable,
so don't forget them.
-[♪ amusing music playing]
-[Chan groans]
Chicken was too predictable, right?
Let's go with charcoal-grilled meat.
-Ben recommended--
-[♪ music fades]
[stammers] All right, fine.
But what's with these?
-[bike bell chimes]
-Ah.
We're going to cross Jamsugyo with these.
It's the fastest way.
I'm sorry, but I'd like to just go now.
[exclaims teasingly]
No way.
[inhales sharply] Can you not ride a bike?
No, it's not that…
-No, it's okay.
-[♪ whimsical music playing]
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
-I'll return them.
-No, I…
I know how to ride a bike, but…
Fine. Let's go, then.
[in English] Okay!
[in Korean] All right.
Since it's boring to just ride there,
how about a bet?
-The last one there buys dinner. Okay?
-[♪ music fades]
No, there's no need…
-Let's just--
-Ready, go!
That's cheating.
[♪ heartwarming song playing]
Oh…
Whoa. Wait…
Hang on! My leg…
Wait, wait!
What is it? What's wrong with your leg?
It's long.
What?
-[chuckles]
-Ah…
[stutters] Geez.
[exclaims]
-[Haran exclaims excitedly]
-[chuckling]
[yells excitedly]
[Haran] Wow!
Wow.
Whoa.
[♪ heartwarming song continuing]
[Chan] Wow, it's beautiful.
Isn't it?
-Wow. The Hangang River is nice.
-[♪ song fades]
[inhales sharply] Were you mimicking me?
But that's not how you do it.
Wow!
Hangang River is really nice.
What's the difference?
-It sounds the same.
-It's different.
[scoffs]
I won, so you're buying.
We haven't even gotten there yet.
[Haran yells excitedly]
[Hayeong in English] Good morning.
[chuckles] Ah!
-[in Korean] Hi, Hadam.
-[in English] Good morning.
[in Korean] You know
Yougyum's coming today, right?
He's coming at 7:00 p.m.,
so don't be late.
Of course. We've been waiting
impatiently for this day.
We'll have you rascals
sit down in front of us
while we look him over from head to toe…
Hey! I'm not done talking.
You did go on for quite a bit.
[sighs heavily]
Haran, she can't be serious
about getting married, can she?
I don't know. We'll see.
[sighs softly]
CHEONGSOL BASEBALL TEAM CHA YOUGYUM
IS JOINING THE MAJOR LEAGUE
[indistinct chatter]
No way. It's Han Sora.
She came to school today?
[Yougyum] What? Who are you?
Why do you want my number?
[chuckles softly]
Because I'm interested in you, of course.
[students exclaim]
I'm not interested in you at all.
And I have a girlfriend.
[Hadam] Yougyum.
Hey, Hadam.
[Yougyum chuckles]
What's going on?
It's nothing.
Ah. Is she your girlfriend?
[scoffs] I'll see you later.
Who is she? Do you know her?
Not at all.
It's the last time I'll even speak to her.
Hey, don't you know? It's her.
-Han Sora, the girl group trainee--
-Hadam!
Have a good day. I'll see you later.
-[chuckles awkwardly]
-[♪ amusing music playing]
-She must really like you.
-[Yougyum] Be quiet, will you?
Come on!
-[player 1] She's so pretty, though.
-[player 2] Right?
[Yougyum] Shut up, you guys.
[Changmo] She has her eyes set on you.
You should date her.
[Yougyum] Be quiet. Shut up.
[player 3] That's the problem
with handsome guys.
"Han Sora"?
[♪ music ends]
[pens rattle]
[sighs softly]
[pen scraping]
Hmm? [exclaims]
[sighs softly]
-[sighs]
-[phone ringing]
This is Design Team 1 of Nana Atelier--
[Nana] Why isn't anyone picking up?
Why are you calling here?
This is urgent. Listen carefully.
It's a womenswear lecture,
but I brought menswear materials.
-That's on me. We don't have much time.
-Taxi! Taxi! Over here!
[Nana] I need you here in 30 minutes.
-[Haran gasping] What do I do?
-[car honks]
[chuckles]
-Hey, my neighbor!
-Oh… Do you have some time?
Sure, I'm totally free.
I rented this car, so I'm taking a drive--
[sighs in relief] That's great! Then…
Then can you…
I have an urgent meeting,
but I can't get a cab.
It's a 15-minute drive.
Please give me a ride.
-[Chan] Well, I…
-[panting]
But I…
-[panting] Yeah?
-[car honks]
[chuckles awkwardly] All right.
[sighs]
Do you know you're driving
20 km an hour right now?
You can drive up to 60 here.
I'm sorry, but can't you go a bit faster?
I only have 20 minutes left.
-Okay.
-[sighs]
[car honking]
-[high-pitched ringing]
-[♪ tense music playing]
-[tires screeching]
-Watch out!
[tires screech]
-[car honking]
-[breathing shakily]
[motorcycle driver] Hey!
Hey, get out.
Get out of the car.
[♪ music fades]
-[sighs]
-I almost got hit because of you.
-You can't just cut in like that.
-[stutters]
I'm sorry. I'll take care of any damages.
Uh…
Okay. I'll pick it up right away.
I'm so sorry.
[motorcycle engine revving]
[breathes deeply]
[grunts] Ms. Song, look at me.
I'm sorry about that.
But everything's fine.
I took care of everything. It's fine.
Are you okay?
Are you sure you're not hurt?
[gasping] I shouldn't have
asked you for a ride.
Nothing happened,
and no one's hurt. It's fine.
-[cell phone vibrating]
-[Haran sighs]
MS. KIM
I'm sorry, but I don't think
I can take you. Uh…
There's a cab over there.
You're in a hurry, so go.
I'll take care of everything here,
so don't worry.
[♪ soft emotional music playing]
[Haran] Getting close to someone
is really difficult…
-No, it's scary for me.
-[sighs]
If no one is special to me,
then at least nothing bad will happen.
[sighs wearily]
[gasps]
[both] Earlier…
[sighs]
[exhales heavily]
I'm sorry about what happened earlier.
No, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have forced you like that.
It was because of your ear, right?
It seemed that way.
[♪ music fades]
-[high-pitched ringing]
-[car honk echoes]
[tires screech]
A few years ago,
Ben got injured because of me.
There was a honk on my left side,
but I couldn't react properly,
like earlier.
Since then, I told myself
I would never give anyone a ride,
but…
Today was the first time,
so I guess I was anxious.
I'm sorry.
You're scared
of bad things happening,
but I made you go through that.
Your free trial
is proving to be effective, though.
Back at the Hangang River,
and in the car earlier,
it helped me a lot.
[♪ heartwarming music playing]
I don't exactly have good memories
about Jamsugyo.
I thought I'd only have sad memories
about it forever,
but I realized I could smile there.
Perhaps I can overwrite
those sad memories, too.
I thought that for the first time.
And I was really scared back in the car,
but I recovered quickly thanks to you.
If it were a few days ago,
I would have just tried to flee again.
But I won't now.
At least until the trial is over,
I won't enter my cave again.
So don't blame yourself, okay?
[inhales sharply, sighs] I'm relieved.
To be honest,
I was pretty scared.
You just mustered up your courage,
and I was worried you'd run away again.
I said we'd have fun,
but I thought I'd already ruined it.
[Chan chuckles softly]
Keep teaching me.
I'll do my best to learn.
I'll get going now. Bye.
Okay. Bye.
[♪ music fades]
Ah.
I actually don't like…
everything being okay and only having fun.
That's fake friendship.
Being able to tell each other
when you're not okay
is real friendship, right?
[sighs softly]
So let's tell each other in advance
if something's wrong
so we won't have to feel guilty
like today.
All right. [inhales sharply]
But you should stop that
if you want real friendship.
Stop what?
You don't have to worry so much
about my hearing.
What? Me?
[♪ lighthearted music playing]
-I wasn't worried about that at all.
-[chuckles] It's pretty obvious, you know.
Ever since you found out,
you've been standing to my right.
I'm usually fine,
so you don't have to do that, okay?
Well, it's been a long time
since I made a new friend,
so I'm not really sure what I have to do.
You seem mature,
but you're a picky eater.
You love Mr. Park's coffee,
you ride a bike very well,
and you pretend not to be,
but you're pretty caring.
What?
This is how you become friends.
Slowly, without forcing anything,
by finding out small things
about each other.
I also don't like oysters.
They're like snot.
What? Snot?
I just told you more about myself.
-Is this not how you do it?
-[chuckles]
It is. That's right.
Give me your hand. I'll give you a stamp.
Here. A "great job" stamp.
[chuckles]
I told you a secret,
so next time it's your turn.
It doesn't have to be anything big.
Just a small one.
[chuckles]
Bye, then.
Bye.
[inhales sharply, sighs]
A secret…
[sighs softly]
[♪ music ends]
[Hadam] Hmm. Hair, check.
Your outfit's nice… [squeals]
and your face is even nicer.
-You're perfect.
-[sighs wearily]
I'm so nervous.
I wasn't even this nervous
at the Comets press conference.
It's okay to be nervous.
Just be yourself.
Wow. Hearing you say that
suddenly made me calm.
[chuckles softly] Then hold my hand.
[whines]
I'm actually really nervous. [giggles]
Just trust me. Let's do this.
-Okay.
-[door opens]
You're finally here.
Let's see who this guy is.
Hello. I'm Cha Yougyum.
[♪ pensive music playing]
-[traffic light beeping]
-[Yougyum] It's a green light!
[grunts]
[sighs]
[car horns honking]
[exclaiming]
[car honks]
-[tires screech]
-[car honks loudly]
[cars honking]
Why did you get here late?
Who did you help?
[Yougyum] An elderly woman.
She was standing in the middle
of the crosswalk at a red light.
It looked dangerous.
Are you all right, ma'am?
Where are you headed?
It seemed like she might have dementia.
-[♪ music continues]
-Oh…
[♪ music ends]
[gasps, exclaims]
It's nice to meet you. [chuckles]
Hadam doesn't know,
so pretend you never saw me.
[giggles]
Isn't he handsome?
[Hadam giggles]
What? Yougyum, are you crying?
-Huh?
-[♪ amusing music playing]
[chuckling nervously] Oh, I…
[stuttering] I'm just so happy
to meet your grandmother.
I couldn't help it.
[both chuckle]
[Hadam sighs]
-[line ringing]
-Why aren't they picking up?
[♪ music fades]
-[sighs]
-[line disconnects]
My sisters aren't picking up.
We should just…
Why are you sweating?
-Is it hot?
-Oh.
I'm not feeling so well.
I'll come back when her sisters are here.
-What?
-Will you?
I'll see you again next time.
See you at school.
[♪ amusing music playing]
[Hadam] Yougyum!
What was that, Grandma?
You didn't even look at him
and didn't say a word. [groans]
He left because
you made him uncomfortable.
Hadam.
I'm not feeling well today, either--
Haran and Hayeong didn't even come.
He's really important to me.
How can you do this?
Did you think I was joking
about getting married?
-Hadam.
-I can't believe this!
[breathing heavily]
-Yougyum!
-Hadam!
-[door opens, closes]
-[sighs]
How could he be… [sighs]
Hayeong!
-Why are you so late?
-Well, I…
-There's chalk on your face.
-Yougyum!
[Hayeong mumbles]
[Haran] Hadam!
Did Yougyum leave?
I'm sorry, things were hectic.
I didn't notice the time.
I'm really sorry, too.
We have a fitting tomorrow,
but the sample--
Right. Sure.
I'm sure you had your reasons.
It's fine.
You're so generous.
You have a big heart…
-Or maybe not.
-[♪ whimsical music playing]
You're not okay, are you?
You're angry, right?
Yes. Very.
I'm holding back my anger,
so don't talk to me.
Are you jealous because I'm doing
way better than you? [groans angrily]
You're so annoying!
-[sighs]
-[Hayeong] Oh, no…
[door thuds, opens]
Grandma, why did Yougyum leave so quickly?
Um… He must not be feeling well.
[grunts] I should go shower. Go upstairs.
What?
Doesn't Grandma seem like she's unwell?
Maybe the lecture was pretty tough.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
-[traffic light beeping]
-[indistinct chatter]
[car honk echoes]
[♪ music continues]
Are you all right, ma'am?
Where are you headed?
[grunts softly] I'm not sure.
I can't remember where I was going.
It's okay. We'll cross the street together
when it's a green light.
-[♪ music fades]
-[sighs]
[sniffles]
Hadam. I'm sorry.
Tell Yougyum to come back next time, okay?
[sighs defeatedly]
[sniffles]
[sniffs]
-[♪ soft emotional music playing]
-[exhales]
[sniffles]
[deep inhale, sighs]
[sighs]
[♪ music fades]
[cell phone vibrating]
Yes, Mr. Cha.
Lunch?
I'd love that. I'll head there now.
-Okay.
-Ms. Song.
Yes?
Ms. Kim is asking for you.
Me?
[gasps]
Wait. I went there last time,
but she'd already gone home.
Why do you keep playing pranks?
It doesn't suit you.
I mixed up the date.
She wanted to see you today.
You should go see her now.
You mean it?
[♪ amusing music playing]
[sighs] All right, then.
Yes, Mr. Cha.
I don't think I can go. I'm sorry.
I don't know. She keeps asking for me.
MEN'S HEALTH
SEONGWON BRANCH
[♪ music ends]
-[footsteps approaching]
-[knock on door]
[exclaims softly] Just a minute.
Come in.
Ms. Kim.
I heard you asked for me.
Were you dreaming? I didn't ask for you.
-Get out. Don't bother me.
-Eh?
What's with Mr. Yeon?
Why does he keep lying to me?
I'd like you to talk to yourself outside.
Okay.
I'll excuse myself, then.
-[door opens, closes]
-[footsteps leaving]
Did I ask for her?
I don't think I did.
[sighs heavily]
[♪ mysterious music plays]
[♪ music fades]
Sol, the shoulder is 17 inches, right?
-[Sol] Oh. One moment, please.
-[Hayeong] Okay.
What's going on? Something's off.
Something's different from usual.
What? What's different?
[Remy] What?
-[screams]
-[♪ whimsical music playing]
Right. It's that.
She hasn't pushed the button once today.
-[gasps]
-[Sol exclaims]
You're right!
[both exclaim]
-[Seung-gyu] Are you okay?
-[Sol] I'm sorry.
[mumbling]
[Remy] Two, four…
-Look at the time.
-[♪ music fades]
-[staff chatter indistinctly]
-What a surprise.
[Haran] What? Gyeongju?
The costume team, too?
Yes, it was our director's idea.
He said a better understanding
of the background
would help with the costumes.
Right.
We won't be able to capture the details
with the script alone.
Then shall we…
[whooshing]
Ah.
My schedule's packed,
so you can go as long as
it doesn't interfere with other work.
I'm ready to go!
I've been buried in fabric dust.
I'll finally get some fresh air!
You're not going on a picnic.
Get fresh air on your day off.
You know I'll work hard there.
Picnic, beep.
Business trip, ding ding ding. [chuckles]
I think two nights will be enough
for your team. Is that okay?
Then our costume team
will head there on Thursday.
All right.
[♪ upbeat song playing over speakers]
[mumbling]
Hey, Yang Changmo!
Hey, Hadam.
Where's Yougyum?
He said he had to go somewhere.
Oh… Wasn't he meeting up with you?
Huh?
How are we going to get through today?
We do it every day.
Yougyum!
Hey.
Go ahead.
Sorry about yesterday.
Let's talk after your practice.
No, I'm sorry.
I didn't take care of myself properly.
But sorry, Changmo asked to see me later.
Maybe he needs my advice
on something. [chuckles awkwardly]
[Hadam chuckles softly]
Yougyum, what are you doing?
You said you're meeting Changmo.
Did you meet him?
[Yougyum] What? Yes, why?
-Is something up?
-Huh?
[♪ whimsical music playing]
No, I was just calling.
Bye, then.
[line disconnects]
[♪ music continues]
Oh?
Yougyum…
Yougyum!
[Sora] I'll see you later.
I wanted to meet you, too.
Are you happy? Enjoying your date?
-Hadam!
-How could you meet Han Sora--
-[♪ music ends]
-[woman] Hadam.
[Hadam gasps]
-What are you doing here?
-I'm here too.
What? You were waiting
in front of our school?
You didn't even know his face.
How could we not know him?
He was even on the news.
-[chuckles shyly]
-[♪ lighthearted music playing]
They threatened you, didn't they?
That's why you lied to me, right?
I told him not to tell you
because we wanted to apologize.
No, there's no need.
I left early
because I wasn't feeling well.
But who's Han Sora?
You said something about Han Sora.
I don't know what you're talking about.
[exclaims softly] Let's eat.
[gasps]
[Hadam] Mmm. This is good.
[cell phone vibrating]
Hey, Hadam.
-[Hadam] You said you're meeting Changmo.
-Huh?
Did you meet him?
What? Yes, why? Is something up?
Huh? No, I was just calling.
[sighs softly] Okay.
[line disconnects]
There's a visitor? Who…
[Yougyum] Is it pretty bad?
[Nana] My mind goes blank
from time to time.
I sometimes buy the same book
two or three times.
I'm usually fine,
but there are days I'm not,
like the day I met you.
Uh… Did you see a doctor?
I got a basic checkup,
and they said there were signs.
I scheduled a follow-up exam
in a few weeks.
But at my age,
you can sense it.
It's probably right.
-[♪ soft emotional music playing]
-[sighs]
I'm not sure what to do.
You should tell your family--
No.
I have to focus on what I can do now.
I don't know how much longer
I'll be myself.
I have to take care of things
and receive treatment while I can.
I'm sorry to burden you,
but please do me a favor.
[Hayeong] The fries here are good.
[Haran] Hadam, try this.
You like these, right?
[Nana] Haran has already lost
many loved ones.
I don't want to be a burden to her now.
Hayeong is always so loud
and quick to laugh.
But if she finds out about my condition,
she won't be able to smile again.
Hadam's in her senior year.
She needs to focus on her studies.
I won't be the reason she falls apart.
So please...
For now,
keep this a secret.
I don't have much time.
[♪ music fades]
[groans] How badly did they scrape it?
Are you the one who called me
about the accident?
[♪ amusing music playing]
I did call you, but there was no accident.
What… Then why would you say
there was an accident?
Hang on.
It's you, isn't it?
-I have it all planned out.
-Mr. Cha Min?
[Min] I'll treat you to something nice.
[tires screeching]
-[exclaiming]
-[♪ music ends]
[tires screeching]
[window whirring]
[scoffs]
What was that? What's with him?
The guy in the hotel parking lot
who reversed into me.
Who are you--
That's not your business.
Why don't you sort out
all the women you've been juggling?
What are you saying?
Who are you to order me around?
It would be best
to say you got transferred abroad
so no one feels hurt.
If you don't stop acting like a scumbag,
we'll be meeting again.
-[scoffs]
-[car lock beeps]
[Min] Hey!
That's what you call being a scumbag.
Do you want the other one broken, too?
Whether you break it or not,
just sort out your women problem.
I suggest sending out DMs right now.
Mmm… [singsongs] No, thanks.
I'm not going to.
It's all because I'm popular.
What are you going to do? [gasps]
-[♪ amusing music playing]
-Oh…
Wait. Hey. Hey!
[exclaims] My phone.
[exclaims nervously]
Hey!
If you don't sort them out,
the next thing you'll lose…
won't be your phone.
[Min] Wait.
-Hang on.
-Hello.
I want to schedule a car repair.
My phone's in there.
-What are you doing?
-[whining]
-[♪ music ends]
-I'm heading out! [grunts]
-[car lock beeps]
-[shudders]
-Whoa. Oh…
-I'll drive.
[stutters] What are you doing here?
We're going to Gyeongju.
I'm going to Gyeongju,
but the costume team--
I'm going today, too.
Can you load my luggage?
Oh…
-[♪ lighthearted music playing]
-[car door closes]
Sure…
[Chan inhales sharply]
[Chan] Mmm…
Wow. I feel pretty happy.
You're worried about me.
Worried?
Me?
[clicks tongue] You were worried about
me driving after what happened last time.
When did I…
You're right. [sighs]
It must be your first time
driving on a highway in Korea.
Thanks.
[Haran clears throat]
[♪ music fades]
But do you usually do
field research for animations?
Of course.
-You know Arendelle, right?
-[♪ enchanting music playing]
That was based on
a lakeside town called Hallstatt.
And the ice castle was inspired
by a hotel built of ice in Quebec.
And Won is Korean,
so we're looking
for her background in Korea.
We have to decide
where she grew up and how
so we can blend that into the story.
You had the vibe of a local bum,
but you seem like a pro now.
-[♪ music fades]
-A local bum?
Geez.
I didn't want to say this myself,
but I'll just say it.
I'm pretty competent.
I get lots of job offers, too.
I meant it's nice
seeing you look so excited
talking about work.
-[chuckles]
-[cell phone vibrating]
Hang on.
[grunts]
Hey, Ben.
Well, we're…
We're almost halfway there.
Oh. I'm going with Ms. Song.
It just happened.
See you later.
-[inhales sharply, sighs]
-[line disconnects]
I can smell rain.
[♪ sentimental music playing]
Is it a shower?
[Chan] Mmm.
But I heard it's the smell
of organic matter diffusing,
not the rain.
-What was it again?
-Petrichor.
Right, petrichor.
You're really good at this stuff.
You said something about hypochlorite
at the police station, too.
It seems like you majored
in engineering, not art.
Oh? It stopped. What's going on?
-[mumbles]
-Huh?
Is it not working?
No. Didn't they check this car?
I got it checked.
It's not raining much yet, though.
[thunder rumbles]
-What…
-[exclaims]
Wait. It's raining too much.
Just pull over to the side.
Pull over?
[Haran exclaiming nervously]
UNDER CONSTRUCTION
NO SHOULDER AHEAD
Huh? "No shoulder ahead"?
Then what do we do?
It's not like we can make a road.
-First…
-Check if there are any cars.
Hang on. I'll take care of it.
[♪ whimsical music playing]
Oh no. I can't see anything. What do I do?
Wait.
-Hang on.
-I can't see anything.
[exclaims, grunts]
-What are you doing?
-This won't work.
Check if there are any cars coming!
I can't see anything.
SOMUNGYEONG REST STOP
-It's a rest stop!
-A rest stop?
I can't see the road, though.
I'll keep my eye on the road,
so keep driving.
But I can't see.
I'll count to three,
-so turn right when I get to three.
-Okay.
[Chan] All right…
One, two,
three.
[♪ heartwarming music playing]
SOMUNGYEONG REST STOP
[both sigh in relief]
[sighs]
[sighs softly]
[chuckles softly]
[both chuckle]
[Chan sighs]
Ah…
Take a breather.
I'll call the rental shop.
[Haran] Oh… [grunts]
[♪ music fades]
What? Four to five hours?
The motor's completely out.
We can't fix it here.
I'll take it to a repair shop nearby.
If you want a replacement,
we'll send you another car tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
Yes, we probably won't get there
until tonight.
Okay, Ben. I'll call you again
when we're heading out.
Okay.
[line disconnects]
[shudders]
Here, wipe yourself up.
[stutters] It's fine.
-You really don't listen.
-[sighs]
[♪ sentimental music playing]
[grunts]
[Haran sighs]
How are we going to wait here for hours?
There's someone in Mungyeong Saejae
I can ask for help.
[♪ music ends]
[tires screech]
Seonu Chan!
-[Chan] Wow, that was fast.
-[♪ pleasant music playing]
-You little brat.
-[groans]
You should've told me you came to Korea.
You only called me now?
Sorry.
-Oh, my. [gasps]
-[Chan chuckles]
-Did you take ginseng?
-Yes.
-You look so healthy.
-Right?
-[grunts]
-[chuckles]
Oh, dear.
Goodness.
This is Designer Song Haran,
who's working with me.
-Say hi.
-[sighs]
[Chan] She's my grandmother.
Grandmother?
Hello.
[Chan's grandma chuckles]
I haven't really made
a great first impression.
-Nice to meet you.
-Hello.
-Let's go.
-[groans]
[♪ pleasant music continuing]
-Isn't that a waste?
-You think so? [chuckles]
But we have to empty it out a few times
to get rid of the impurities.
It makes the flavor
much smoother this way.
It's the same with people.
We have to empty ourselves out
from time to time
to clear our heads and soften our hearts.
[sighs contentedly] The color's nice.
-Try it.
-Thank you.
[exclaims] It's hot. Cool it down a bit.
It's okay, it's not hot.
[grunts, exclaims]
You're right. It's not.
How about some coffee?
I brought Mr. Park's coffee beans.
I'll go and…
I'd prefer tea right now.
[chuckles nervously]
-[gasps] It's delicious.
-Right?
Wow.
The teapot and this cup…
Everything here is so beautiful. [gasps]
They were all made by my grandma.
She's a potter.
-[gasps softly]
-The building outside is my studio.
Would you care to take a look
once you're done?
[stutters]
-[scoffs]
-[exclaims, laughs]
Oh…
Yes… I'd love to take a look. [grimaces]
Hey, Chaewon.
What do you mean, you're sorry?
[sniffs]
What are you doing?
Savoring the only meal I'm having
to get my jawline back.
[keyboard clacking]
-[yells]
-[gasps]
-Oh, my gosh.
-Samples are here!
My sweet potato.
[sighs wearily] I feel like
I swallowed a sock.
What is it? Did something piss you off?
-[♪ suspenseful music playing]
-You know the guy I was seeing?
He cheated.
[Seung-gyu exclaims]
The guy who sent the flowers?
That son of a…
[sighs] I shouldn't swear. With who?
With me. I'm the other woman.
He made a ton of social media accounts
and used them to hit on girls.
And I just heard
he's giving out wedding invitations.
That jerk!
Should I just beat him up? [grunts]
Never mind. Just forget it
and pretend nothing happened.
Why would I just forget about it?
[♪ music fades]
[exhales] I'm going to crush him.
♪ Happy wedding to you ♪
♪ Happy wedding, dear Cha Min ♪
♪ Happy wedding… ♪
Ms. Song.
Were you pleased
with your wedding invitations?
If you found out, just go.
I guess it was you.
I was wondering why
some guy was picking a fight.
Was he your boyfriend?
What are you saying?
How would you meet
a boyfriend I don't have?
Boom!
He threatened me with his car
and threw my phone into a mop bucket.
Geez. I should've broken
both his rear-view mirrors.
Tell that jerk to watch his back at night.
Quit the nonsense.
You should watch your back, day and night.
You should sleep with one eye open.
You never know when I'll crush you.
Forget it. Just go.
I'm not done yet.
-[grunts, whines]
-[♪ upbeat music playing]
My nose…
[whines] I paid a fortune for this.
-Hey!
-What?
You.
You'd better stay out of my sight.
Or I'll kick you somewhere else.
[♪ music ends]
[sighs wearily]
[sighs]
Did you go somewhere?
I had a meeting.
Ah…
But is there something wrong?
You seem pretty down.
What? No.
I'm fine.
But why were you riding a cab?
You always drive.
Uh… I had to get it repaired.
Ah. I see.
Head inside.
I'm going to go get some coffee.
I was wondering why
some guy was picking a fight.
I should've broken
both his rear-view mirrors.
"Cha Min." Even his name is nice.
-What do you think, Mr. Yeon?
-I'm not so sure.
-But, Mr. Cha…
-Ms. Kim wants you in her office.
[♪ whimsical music playing]
Are you…
getting it repaired
because of your rear-view mirror?
Yes.
But why…
Are you the one who met Cha Min?
Uh…
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Oh. You really have no idea?
Okay, then I'll just go meet him.
Cha Min's number was…
Are you going to say
"Ms. Kim is asking for you" again?
Yes, Ms. Kim. I'll be there straightaway.
You didn't even get a call.
And she already got off work.
[Taeseok] Yes, I'm on my way.
You're holding your phone upside down!
Gosh, what's with him?
[gasps]
Wait. No way…
-[gasps]
-[♪ lighthearted music playing]
It can't be, right?
[Haran] Wow.
Wow.
[gasps] Wow, they're so beautiful.
Take some you like. [chuckles softly]
-[groans]
-They're not even yours. Huh?
-[clears throat]
-[Haran exclaims] What's this drawing?
-Did you draw this, too?
-[Chan] Oh…
Would you like to try
making something here?
[chuckles softly]
The aprons…
[footsteps thudding]
[♪ pleasant music playing]
[Chan sighs]
I'm done.
-Already?
-[chuckles softly]
-[Haran] Oh, no! Wait.
-[exclaims]
[stutters, sighs in relief]
[chuckles] That was close.
[cell phone vibrating]
Let me take this call.
Sure.
[in English] Hello?
[exclaims, gasps]
[exclaims, speaks in Korean]
It's so pretty.
How about becoming my pupil?
-[chuckles]
-[laughs] I mean it.
Leave me your address and phone number.
I'll fire it nicely and send it to you.
[chuckles] Thank you.
I guess Mr. Seonu
inherited his gift from you.
That drawing was his mother's.
My daughter was an artist too.
Ah. So he took after his mother.
He and my daughter would draw
on any piece of paper they could find.
Wait here.
[♪ music fades]
[gasps]
They're pictures he drew
whenever he came here as a child.
[Haran exclaims, laughs]
He was so excited
when he talked about work.
I guess he really loved drawing.
If his dad hadn't hated it so much,
he would have enjoyed it much more.
Ah. [chuckles]
His father hated him doing art.
But you said his mother was an artist…
Her dream was to go abroad
and study more art.
And Chan's father wanted her
to wait until Chan was older.
-[♪ sentimental music playing]
-Look!
[Chan's dad] Why do we have
to keep arguing over this?
Don't you understand?
Why now? Why do you have
to go abroad to study?
You know it's been my dream
since before we got married. [sighs]
I want to study properly
before it's too late.
Fine. Do it.
You can study here and think about it
again when Chan is older.
You're hardly home anyway!
[sighs] You can stay in your lab
all you want. I'll take Chan--
If you must go,
then leave Chan and go by yourself.
[Chan's grandma]
She still wanted to go so badly.
So I pushed her to follow her dream
and do what she wanted.
She thought she had to settle down quickly
to be with Chan again,
so she pushed herself too hard.
-And she got sick.
-[young Chan sobbing]
Soon after she left the country,
she...
Chan!
Oh, no!
I can't believe what happened…
He said he'd never let Chan paint again.
So he sent him to America.
Chan didn't get to do anything he loved,
and he suffered there.
[♪ music continues]
KSU
KOREA SCIENCE UNIVERSITY
[Chan's grandma] It would've been painful
for Chan's father just to see him paint.
He thinks Chan's mom left to paint...
KOREAN ANIMATORS IN THE GLOBAL SPOTLIGHT
...and died because of it.
[in English] Okay, bye.
[Chan's grandma in Korean] Back then,
my daughter was all I could think about.
But whenever I see Chan,
it breaks my heart.
-[camera clicks]
-If he had his mother,
at least he wouldn't have been hurt
both emotionally and physically.
[Chan] I've also been trapped
in a long winter all by myself.
[♪ music fades]
[door opens]
Oh?
Where's Ms. Song?
-She's washing her hands.
-Oh.
[Chan sighs]
Is it just one-sided at the moment?
What do you mean?
[Chan sighs]
Gosh, Grandma. It's not like that.
Don't be silly.
I can see it clearly.
You have a crush on Ms. Song, don't you?
It's not like that.
She's someone I shouldn't like.
What do you mean, someone you shouldn't…
[gasps] Hey.
Is she married, by any chance?
No, she's not married.
Then why would you say
you shouldn't like her?
[Haran] Ma'am, can I get a towel?
Sure. Hang on.
[sighs]
[sighs heavily] How could I like her?
That would be selfish.
[Chan's grandma] Visit me again next time.
You can come without that chatterbox.
Sure. I'll come without that chatterbox
next time.
-[Haran chuckles]
-[exclaims]
Don't build your friendship
by badmouthing me.
-[laughs]
-[chuckles]
It was so nice to meet you.
-Take care.
-Stay healthy, ma'am.
[♪ pleasant music playing]
Um… Wait.
[Chan's grandma] What's that?
-Pardon me.
-[Chan's grandma gasps]
[Haran] This is really moisturizing.
[both chuckle]
My hands are pretty rough, right?
I'm always touching clay.
Here, use this.
[Chan's grandma exclaims]
I'll get pretty hands thanks to you.
Let's see…
You know, no matter how warm you dress,
you'll catch a cold
if you don't cover your neck.
-I'm okay.
-No, come here.
Here.
Just take it.
You ruined your scarf because of me.
[Chan's grandma] Hmm? Did she?
[gasps] Wow, look.
It looks incredible on a beautiful model.
Nice. This is great.
Thank you. I'll use it well.
[inhales sharply] Grandma.
-[Chan grunts]
-[Chan's grandma chuckles]
I'll come back before I go back to the US.
-[grunts]
-[groans]
You'd better keep your word.
Chan, please. Hmm?
Don't skip your meals. Okay?
Of course. I eat well.
You too, Grandma.
-[Chan's grandma] Don't worry.
-[Chan] Okay.
Bye!
Drive safely!
[♪ music fades]
[Chan inhales sharply]
Wait. Let's check the windshield wipers
one more time.
-Again?
-Yes.
-Are we good?
-Wait.
[wipers thudding]
Okay. Done. Let's go. [chuckles]
What? Is there something wrong again?
Yes, there is.
Something strange.
What's strange?
Why am I someone you shouldn't like?
What?
Why shouldn't you like me?
[♪ heartwarming music playing]
[Chan's grandma]
You have a crush on Ms. Song, don't you?
It's not like that.
She's someone I shouldn't like.
[Chan's grandma]
What do you mean, someone you shouldn't…
[gasps] Hey.
Is she married, by any chance?
[Chan] No, she's not married.
[Chan's grandma] Then why would you say
you shouldn't like her?
Ma'am, can I get a towel?
[Chan's grandma] Sure. Hang on.
I'm sorry, but I overheard.
I really couldn't understand, though.
You weren't saying
that you didn't like me.
You said you shouldn't like me.
[chuckles] That sounds weird.
[sighs]
It's not like I'm married.
There's nothing between us
that would make it wrong.
What did you mean by that?
Oh… I'm not trying to argue or anything.
I'm just genuinely curious.
Then is it okay if I like you?
[wipers thudding]
[♪ music fades]
[stutters]
[sighs]
[wiper thuds echoing]
[heartbeats echoing]
[♪ romantic song playing]
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
[Haran] The person
who gave me the pen died.
[Chan] What else was there
apart from the explosion?
[Haran] Honestly, I am curious.
You're not telling me everything.
[Chan] The past might not be
as nice as you remember.
I'll explain everything
if you guess it right.
I feel like telling you everything today.
[Haran] Odd.
Odd.
[♪ song fades]
[♪ theme music playing]
IN YOUR RADIANT SEASON
Translated by Juyoung Park